Finding Aid for JJR Inc. photographic slides, 1960s-1990s
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- University of Michigan Project files
  - Flint Campus
    - Numbered Sets (Box 31)
    - Flint Riverfront Campus (Box 31)
    - Flint Riverfront (Box 31)
    - Flint Signage (Box 32)
    - Flint-Thompson Library (Box 32)
    - Willson Park (Box 32)
  - North Campus
    - Aerospace (Box 32)
    - North Campus Aerials (Box 32)
    - Art & Arch Building (Box 32)
    - North Campus (Box 32)
    - North Bell Tower (Box 32)
    - N Campus Dow Building (Box 32)
    - N Campus Engineering Complex (Box 32)
    - N Campus Engineering Building / Naval Architecture (Box 32)
    - Bell Tower Graphics (Box 32)
    - North Campus Images 1995 (Box 32)
    - North Campus Master Plan (Box 32)
    - North Campus Land Plan (Box 33)
    - North Campus-ITI (Box 33)
    - ITIC (Box 33)
    - North Campus Model (Box 33)
    - North Campus Music School (Box 33)
    - Natatorium (Box 33)
    - Pedestrian Bridge (Box 33)
    - Presentation (Box 33)
    - Radrick Farms (Box 33)
    - Residential College (Box 33)
    - Retainer (Box 33)
    - University Senior Community (Box 33)
    - Study (Box 33)
  - South Campus
    - General (Box 33)
    - Aerials (Box 33)
    - Campus Graphics (Box 33)
    - Library Plaza (Box 33)
    - Medical Center Graphics (Box 33)
    - Athletic Campus (Box 33)
    - Tennis Complex (Box 33)
    - Binder-Athletic Field Images (Box 34)
    - Binder-Matthaei Botanical Gardens (Box 34)
- Other Michigan Universities
  - Western Michigan University-Binder (Box 34)
  - Central Michigan University (Box 35)
    - General (Box 35)
  - South Entrance Study (Box 35)
  - MSU Tech Park (Box 35)
  - MSU Horticultural Demonstration Gardens (Box 35)
  - Michigan Tech University
    - Master Plan Update (Box 35)
    - Old College Ave (Box 35)
    - Tech Park (Box 35)
    - Winter Carnival (Box 35)
    - Houghton (Box 35)